[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William"], "LOCATION": ["Kensington Palace"], "TIME": ["this morning"]}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "I -- is there anything that goes on where there are some type of informal protocol with the queen where ahead of time they kind of run names by her, or is she finding out about it like anybody else's?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "The Queen went over to Kensington Palace this morning, primarily to meet her first great grandson, but I think William, he runs everything by her when it comes to the monarchy and how he does things and matters of state.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "I may be -- I'm not saying great either way, but is that really happening?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Right now, certainly it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "TO", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "Is there any chance at this point Weiner gets elected?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "I think it's problematic for both of these candidacies in part because while we have turned this election into a -- sort of a two-ring circus, the bottom line is when you go out and campaign and talk to voters, working people, middle class people, they want to know about affordable housing, they want to know about education opportunities for their kids.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Weiner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Donny"]}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "POS", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "Nik, first of all, are you getting paid by Miss Leathers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "No, Donny, I'm not getting paid at all and I'm not even sure that's her real name.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "What was the reason she came to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "No, she submitted a tip to the site.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2011"], "PERSON": ["Weiner"]}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Was that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Well, what happened was that she actually e-mailed Weiner in 2011 and it wasn't a nice e-mail.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Donny"]}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "So what are -- just as a member of the 300 million people of this country say to yourself before you put something like this out ?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", ":", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "Well, Donny, to me, I look at the Internet and I say, you know, privacy is gone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donny"]}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "Any chance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "I don't see him coming back from it, and Donny, you know, a lot of people -- we've been talking about whether or not he can win.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Huma Abedin"]}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "He comes in your office, what do we do now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "First of all, my disclosure is that I know Huma Abedin very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "As a woman when you're watching Huma, was that feminism at the high point or low point?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Actually it was feminism period.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Huma"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anthony Weiner", "Huma"]}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Is that your take?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "There is no way Anthony Weiner would be in this race if Huma hadn't sign on at the beginning.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "Marc, obviously, any woman could -- you're not buying it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "MD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "I just don't buy it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "How does anybody look past this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "At this point, what we're dealing with is sort of the personal because it's a sexual issue and the professional.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton", "Huma Abedin"]}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJS", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "WP", "RB", "NNP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "If she's in the line next to Hillary, this will not go away and Hillary has a history of when there is a deficit she walks away?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "DT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Look, I love Hillary Clinton as one of my best friends and this obviously is a painful experience for her, because I know she loves Huma Abedin as those of us who know Huma do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary"], "LOCATION": ["Hillary"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington State"]}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "You didn't send that photo to that woman in Washington State?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "I did not send it to that woman in Washington State.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "But you're not 100 percent sure whether the photo is actually you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "I'll say we're doing everything we can to answer that question, but we're doing an investigation.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "But isn't a lot of it just the opportunity?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Well, I -- I think that for a lot of men who are either celebrities because they are in the entertainment business or sports world or because they are well-known elected officials or politicians or hope to be politicians, that they cheat frankly often because they don't believe that there will be consequences that will be serious, that they have the opportunity to do it and because frankly, they have not had to suffer serious consequences in the past.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Is there any thread that you've seen in men over the years -- powerful men, beyond kind the obvious sense of entitlement that causes this behavior?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "This is a little bit of a master of the universe mentality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "I mean, so what is sex addiction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "ONAGHUE: No, I'm going to agree with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", ":", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "And then there's new digital generation -- are they going to look at this a lot with a lot kinder eyes than we would because they're growing up in the digital world and there's a lot more cavalierness to what happens in that virtual world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "NN", "TO", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "I don't think people in their 20s are going to be like -- just think that anything that takes place on the internet is weird certainly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Star, Weiner have any chance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Arrogance will keep him in.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Weiner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donnie"]}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Ben?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Well, Donnie, I think the question is whether you acted on that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Can you profile and follow our children while they walk home and not do anything illegal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "JJ", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "...but like what do we -- how do we get past it (ph)?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "They -- they come to terms with the fact that the assumption is racist.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "How are they doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "Well, they're trying to take something painful and negative and turn it into a positive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "Star, last word?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "I just think that diversity around the table is what's going to move the conversation from talking to action.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]